Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series V. BY-LAWS
  - Sub-Series 204-426. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 426-Auburn Lodge, Auburn, Washington, 1921-1959 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-427. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 427-Santa Fe General Office Lodge, Topeka, Kansas, 1936-1951 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-431. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 431-Pilot Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1921-1954 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-432. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 432-Yakima Lodge, Yakima, Washington, 1934-1959 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-433. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 433-Memphis Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1935-1949 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-435. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 435-Good Fellowship Lodge, Newark, New Jersey, 1953-1959 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-438. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 438-Ivanhoe Lodge, Independence, Missouri, 1944-1959 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-439. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 439-Decatur Lodge, Decatur, Illinois, 1922-1946 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-441. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 441-Portsmouth Lodge, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-443. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 443-Old Colony Lodge, St. John's, Newfoundland, Canada, 1939-1955 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-444. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 444-Dan Kenny Lodge, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1942-1956 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-445. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 445-Salisbury Lodge, Salisbury, North Carolina, 1921-1959 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-446. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 446-St. Louis Lodge, Madison, Illinois, 1921-1959 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-449. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 449-Sunshine Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1934-1959 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-450. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 450-Signal Mountain Lodge, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-451. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 451-New Deal Lodge, Youngstown, Ohio, 1935-1959 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-459. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 459-Evergreen Lodge, Normal, Illinois, 1951-1956 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-462. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 462-Progressive Lodge, Dracut, Massachusetts, 1920-1956 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-464. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 464-Elkhart Lodge, Elkhart, Indiana, 1925-1958 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-473. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 473-Southern Lodge, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-474. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 474-Victory Lodge, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1939-1951 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-486. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 486-Hornell Accounting Bureau Lodge, Hornell, New York, 1936-1956 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-491. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 491-Premier Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1953-1959 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-497. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 497-Maple City Lodge, Hornell, New York, 1935-1947 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-504. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 504-Pacific Fruit Express General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1940-1959 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-507. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 507-Bluff City Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1941-1952 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-508. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 508-Roanoke Lodge, Roanoke, Virginia, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-509. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 509-Erie Lodge, Marion, Ohio, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-511. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 511-Royal Blue Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1921-1958 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-512. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 512-Dupo Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1923-1959 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-513. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 513-Council Bluffs Lodge, Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-514. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 514-Brigham Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1944-1958 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-518. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 518-William Penn Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1931-1959 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-519. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 519-Wheeling Lodge, Wheeling, West Virginia, 1926-1960 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-520. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 520-Terminal Lodge, Newark, New Jersey, 1940-1951 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-521. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 521-St. Clair Lodge, University City, Missouri, 1921-1959 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-522. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 522-Atlanta Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1933-1959 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-523. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 523-Sedalia Lodge, Sedalia, Missouri, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-528. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 528-Great Falls Lodge, Great Falls, Montana, 1936-1945 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-530. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 530-Hermitage Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-533. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 533-Quincy Lodge, Quincy, Illinois, 1923-1929 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-539. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 539-Capital City Lodge, Montgomery, Alabama, 1943-1952 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-540. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 540-Central Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1922-1951 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-542. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 542-National Lodge, Decatur, Illinois, 1924-1957 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-543. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 543-Cotton Belt Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1936-1959 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-544. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 544-Alpha Lodge, Meridian, Mississippi, 1921-1959 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-545. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 545-Wayne Lodge, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1932-1959 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-548. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 548-Akron Lodge, Akron, Ohio, 1938-1954 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-549. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 549-Galewood Lodge, Carpentersville, Illinois, 1928-1959 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-551. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 551-Jubilee Lodge, Channel, Newfoundland, Canada, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 204-553. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 553-Louisville, Kentucky, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-554. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 554-Victory Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1953-1959 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Lodge No. 554-Victory Lodge, Maplewood, Missouri, 1926-1952 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Lodge No. 554-Victory Lodge, Maplewood, Missouri, 1926-1952 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-555. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 555-Barstow Lodge, Barstow, California, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-556. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 556-East St. Louis, Illinois, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-557. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 557-Mobile Lodge, Mobile, Alabama, 1927-1956 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-567. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 567-Monumental Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1923-1953 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 204-569. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 569-Arrowhead Lodge, Rialto, California, 1951-1959 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 204-571. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 571-Witchita Lodge, Wichita, Kansas, 1937-1959 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 204-559. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 559-Clinchfield Lodge, Erwin, Tennessee, 1937-1951 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 294-560. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 560-Parkersburg Lodge, Parkersburg, West Virginia, 1944-1951 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 204-572. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 572-Tri-State Lodge, Elkhart, Indiana, 1922-1938 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-574. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 574-Illinois City Lodge, Allon, Illinois, 1945-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-577. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 577-Pacific Fruit Express Lodge, Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1941-1950 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-587. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 587-Quaker City Lodge, Levittown, Pennsylvania, 1938-1959 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-588. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 588-Duachita Lodge, Monroe, Louisiana, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-589. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 589-General Office Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1940-1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-590. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 590-Keystone Lodge, Levittown, Pennsylvania, 1938-1969 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-591. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 591-Steel City Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1954-1956 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-592. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 592-Talbot Lodge, Lynchurst, Ontario, Canada, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Nov. 5, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 204-593. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 593-St. Paul Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1922-1954 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-595. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 595-General Pershing Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1922-1953 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-596. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 596-South Water Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-601. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 601-Northern Lodge, Fort Scott, Kansas, 1936-1959 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-602. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 602-Los Angeles Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1942-1958 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-604. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 604-Winston Lodge, Hammond, Indiana, 1941-1957 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-610. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 610-Arch City Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1946-1953 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-612. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 612-Reading Federation of Clerks Lodge, West Leesport, Pennsylvania, 1951-1953 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-615. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 615-Missouri Lodge, Maplewood, Missouri, 1923-1959 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-616. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 616-Pottsville Lodge, St. Clair, Pennsylvania, 1943-1951 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-617. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 617-Sagebrush Lodge, Elko, Nevada, 1943-1959 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-620. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 620-Garret W. Daly Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-621. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 621-Fond Du Lac Lodge, Fond Du Lac, Wisconsin, 1924-1959 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-623. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 623-Readville Lodge, Dorchester, Massachusetts, 1921-1936 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-627. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 627-Little Giant Lodge, Cattle Shannon, Pennsylvania, 1924-1950 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-630. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 630-Pacific Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1945-1959 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-633. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 633-Eastern Lodge, Aurora, Illinois, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-639. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 639-Uncle Sam Lodge, Fort Thomas, Kentucky, 1947-1949 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-640. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 640-Penn-Harris Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-641. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 641-Ogden Lodge, Ogden, Utah, 1939-1956 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-642. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 642-Murphysboro Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1944-1959 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-647. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 647-Chester W. Harrison Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1931-1959 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-649. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 649-Owensboro Lodge, Owensboro, Kentucky, 1944-1959 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-650. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 650-Prince Arthur Lodge, Fort William, Ontario, Canada, 1948-1959 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-653. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 653-Reading General Office Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1949-1959 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-654. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 654-Houston Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1938-1959 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-659. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 659-Minute Man Lodge, Lowell, Massachusetts, 1945-1950 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-669. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 669-Middletown Lodge, Middletown, Ohio, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-674. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 674-Virginian Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-676. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 676-White Rose Lodge, York, Pennsylvania, 1920-1959 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-677. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 677-Hamilton Lodge, Obetz, Ohio, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-679. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 679-Chicago and Northwestern Lodge, Lombard, Illinois, 1921-1959 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-681. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 681-Pittsburgh Station Employees Lodge, Verona, Pennsylvania, 1940-1953 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-682. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 682-Helen Hill Lodge, Lancaster, Ohio, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-685. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 685-Reservation Bureau Lodge, Valley Stream, Long Island, New York, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-686. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 686-Muskogee Lodge, Muskogee, Oklahoma, 1946-1951 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-688. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 688-Acorn Lodge, Roanoke, Virginia, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-689. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 689-Commercial Lodge, Springfield, Missouri, 1921-1936 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-691. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 691-Louisville and Nashville Lodge, Birmingham, Alabama, 1945-1957 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-700. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 700-Midland Lodge, Springfield, Illinois, 1941-1959 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-705. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 705-Progressive Ticket Lodge, Sunnyside, New York, 1946-1956 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-709. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 709-Tippecaoue Lodge, Lafayette, Indiana, 1935-1956 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-715. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 715-Old Pueblo Lodge, Tucson, Arizona, 1940-1958 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-717. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 717-Central Vermont Lodge, St. Albans, Vermont, 1940-1952 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-718. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 718-Zone Lodge, Manhasset, New York, 1938-1945 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-719. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 719-Fort Pitt Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-723. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 723-Victory Lodge, Hornell, New York, 1935-1959 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 204-726. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 726-Penco Lodge, Freedom, Pennsylvania, 1944-1952 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-729. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 729-Bridge City Lodge, Trafford, Pennsylvania, 1944-1955 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-730. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 730-Popular Bluffs Lodge, DeSoto, Missouri, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 204-734. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 734-Multnomah Lodge, Portland, Oregon, 1934-1959 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-737. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 737-Overland Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1941-1959 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-740. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 740-Almo Lodge, Parsons, Kansas, 1954-1958 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-741. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 741-DeSota Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1941-1951 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-744. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 744-Victory Lodge, McComb, Mississippi, 1949-1959 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 204-745. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 745-Loyalty Lodge, Jackson, Mississippi, 1943-1959 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 204-746. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 746-New York Central Lodge, South Bend, Indiana, 1941-1959 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 204-751. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 751-Flamingo Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 204-753. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 753-Mingo Lodge, Williamson, West Virginia, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 204-758. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 758-Logan Lodge, Altoona, Pennsylvania, 1940-1958 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 204-763. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 763-Challenger Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1940-1952 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 204-769. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 769-Caddo Lodge, Marshall, Texas, 1937-1959 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 204-772. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 772-Ozark Lodge, Springfield, Missouri, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 204-774. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 774-Woodlawn Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1932-1954 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 204-780. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 780-Opportunity Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1951-1958 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 204-783. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 783-Harrison Lodge, Keyport, New Jersey, 1951-1959 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 204-785. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 785-Whitefish Lodge, Whitefish, Montana, 1921-1959 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 204-786. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 786-Tri City Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1938-1959 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 204-790. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 790-North Terminal Lodge, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1926-1959 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 204-791. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 791-Reynolds Lodge, Johnson City, New York, 1941-1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-793. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 793-Schuyler Lodge, Albany, New York, 1952-1956 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-801. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 801-Fulton Division Lodge, Fulton, Kentucky, 1929-1959 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-802. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 802-Oakland Lodge, Oakland, California, 1922-1954 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-813. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 813-Winslow Lodge, Winslow, Arizona, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-816. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 816-Forest City Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1924-1948 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-820. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 820-Stockton Division Lodge, Stockton, California, 1921-1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-821. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 821-William Franklin Lodge, Altoona, Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-825. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 825-Marion Lodge, Marion, Ohio, 1929-1949 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-831. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 831-Inland Empire Lodge, Spokane, Washington, 1936-1959 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-834. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 834-San Diego Lodge, Lakeside, California, 1948-1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-836. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 836-Charles Sievers Lodge, Bradley, Illinois, 1932-1947 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-840. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 840-Terminal Lodge, Holbrook, Massachusetts, 1944-1955 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-841. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 841-Flager Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1937-1959 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-843. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 843-Java Lodge, Coffeyville, Kansas, 1942-1947 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-846. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 846-Detroit and Cleveland Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1942-1944 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-848. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 848-Ponce de Leon Lodge, St. Augustine, Florida, 1945-1959 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-850. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 850-Toronto Lodge, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1938-1951 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-851. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 851-Point Edward, Ontario, Canada, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-853. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 853-Carbondale Lodge, Carbondale, Pennsylvania, 1922-1948 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-852. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 852-Franklin D. Roosevelt Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1937-1956 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-854. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 854-San Francisco Lodge, Palo Alto, California, 1927-1959 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-856. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 856-Coastwise Lodge, New York, New York, 1940-1950 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-858. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 858-James J. Mullen Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1946-1948 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-861. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 861-Albany Lodge, Albany, New York, 1943-1958 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-863. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 863-Ravenswood Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1926-1959 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-864. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 864-Livestock Handlers Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-865. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 865-Security Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1953 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-869. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 869-Minnesota Transfer Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1944-1952 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-877. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 877-Terminal Lodge, New Haven, Connecticut, 1939-1950 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-879. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 879-Creston Lodge, Creston, Iowa, 1926-1927 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-882. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 882-Service Lodge, Springfield, Missouri, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-883. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 883-San Jose Lodge, San Jose, California, 1950-1959 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-885. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 885-Pickwick Lodge, Lakewood, Ohio, 1934-1959 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-887. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 887-Massachusetts Bay Lodge, Portland, Maine, 1948-1952 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-890. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 890-General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1921-1959 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-892. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 892-Seymour Lodge, Seymour, Indiana, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-893. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 893-Peoria Lodge, Peoria, Illinois -1921-59 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-897. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 897-Jere Baxter Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee/ Lodge No. 897, Elizabeth River Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1938-1959 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      1950-59; May, 1938.
  - Sub-Series 204-899. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 899-Vineyard Line Lodge, New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-900. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 900-Pocatello Lodge, Pocatello, Idaho, 1921-1959 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-901. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 901-Beaumont Lodge, Beaumont, Texas, 1944-1959 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-902. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 902-Floyd B. Olson Memorial Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1941-1958 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-904. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 904-Shandala Lodge, Averill Park, New York, 1943-1959 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-906. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 906-Wabash Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1957 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-907. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 907-Dallas-Austin Lodge, Ennis, Texas, 1948-1959 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-908. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 908-Tip-up Lodge, Washington, Illinois, 1953-1959 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-909. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 909-Pony Express Lodge, Ogden, Utah, 1941-1951 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-911. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 911-Central District Lodge, Roseville, California, 1938-1954 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-915. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 915-Beardstown Lodge, Beardstown, Illinois, 1921-1959 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-920. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 920-Cotton Belt General Office Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1937-1952 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-922. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 922-Bison City Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-926. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 926-Golden Spike Lodge, Roy, Utah, 1925-1959 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-928. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 928-Pacific Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1941-1950 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-930. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 930-Black Diamond Lodge, Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, 1938-1959 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-932. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 932-Blue Ridge Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1921-1945 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 204-933. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 933-Gateway Lodge, Peoria, Illinois, 1938-1959 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-936. Bylaws